Desert Botanical Laboratory of the Carnegie Institution records, 1903-1985
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: General Records and Correspondence, 1905-1938
  - Correspondence Regarding Plant Exchanges and Collecting, 1912-1937
    - Correspondence: Ferris, Roxana S., Dudley Herbarium, Stanford University. 1934-1936 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Gentry, Howard Scott, Sonora, Mexico and California. 1934-1937 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Graham, Edward H., Carnegie Museum, Pittsburgh. 1929-1936 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Hester, J. P. 1930-1934 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Hoffman, Ralph, Santa Barbara Museum of Natural History. 1928-1932 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Johnston, Ivan M., Arnold Arboretum, Harvard University. 1934-1937 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Kerney, T. H., Peebles, R. H., Tidestrom, I., U. S. D. A., Bureau of Plant Industry. 1928-1937 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Kraus, E. J., Department of Botany, University of Chicago. 1929-1934 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Labordere, Marcel, Paris. 1931-1932 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Manson, James W., Nogales, Arizona. 1932-1935 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Miege, E., Rabat, Morocco. 1930-1937 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Rethaller, Marcel, Baja California. 1934-1937 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Standley, Paul C., Simms, S. C., Gregg, C. C., Field Museum of Natural History, Chicago. 1931-1937 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Swingle, Walter, T., U. S. D. A., Bureau of Plant Industry. 1925-1935 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Whitehead, Jack, Boyce Thompson Southwestern Arboretum. 1933-1937 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Wiggins, Ira L., Dudley Herbarium, Stanford University. 1932-1937 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Wynd, F. Lyle, Washington University, St. Louis. 1936-1937 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence With Scientific Societies, 1915-1937
    - Correspondence: American Association for the Advancement of Science. 1915-1937 (Box 20, Folder 1-6)
      Includes material on the AAAS Population Symposium, 1930.
    - Correspondence: Prentiss, Elliott C., American Association for the Advancement of Science. 1920-1928 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Botanical Society of America and American Society of Plant Physiologists. 1920-1931 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Ecological Society of America. 1919-1937 (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
      Includes correspondence about its publication, Ecology, and articles submitted by MacDougal and others. Also correspondence with Barrington Moore, President.
    - Correspondence: Cactus and Succulent Society of America. 1930-1937 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      Includes correspondence about its journal and Shreve articles.
  - University of Arizona Correspondence, 1909-1937
    - Correspondence: Anderson, Ernest, Department of Chemistry. 1925-1927 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Brown, J. G., Department of Botany, Department of Plant Pathology. 1910-1935 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Buehrer, T. F., Department of Chemistry, Agriculture Experiment Station. 1928-1933 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Crider, F. J., Department of Horticulture, Boyce Thompson Southwestern Arboretum. 1922-1933 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Doublass, Andrew, E., Steward Observatory. 1920-1929 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Forbes, Robert H., Agriculture Experiment Station. 1909, 1919-1924 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Kleinsmid, Rufus B. von, President, University of Arizona, President, University of Southern California. 1916-1924 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Lockwood, Franck, C., Acting President, University of Arizona, Dean, College of Letters, Arts & Sciences. 1921-1930 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Marvin, Cloyd H., President, University of Arizona. 1923-1926 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Shantz, Homer L., Department of Botany, University of Illinois, President, University of Arizona. 1927-1933 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Thornber, J. J., Agriculture Experiment Station. 1913-1934 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Vinson, A. E., Agriculture Experiment Station. 1913-1926 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Vorhies, Charles T., Agriculture Experiment Station. 1922-1935 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Wilde, Arthur H., President, University of Arizona. 1913-1914 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding the University of Arizona Presidency. 1914-1927 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding various University of Arizona topics. 1912-1937 (Box 21, Folder 16)
      Includes Tucson Chamber of Commerce letters regarding the Munk Library, departmental reorganization, a metal tower on the roof of the Mines Building, etc.
  - Correspondence Regarding Equipment and Supplies, 1906-1938
    - Correspondence: Arthur H. Thomas Co., Philadelphia. 1910-1935 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Correspondence: Braun Corporation, Los Angeles. 1910-1933 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Braun-Knecht-Heimann Co., San Francisco. 1920-1929 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Central Scientific Co., Chicago. 1920-1937 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: James W. Conway, Atlanta. 1928 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Fred S. Carver, New York City. 1929-1931 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Harris Laboratories, Tuckahoe, New York. 1921 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Fred C. Henson, Co., Pasadena, California. 1928-1936 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Julien P. Friez & Sons, Baltimore, Maryland. 1910-1938 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Standard Oil Company of California. 1928, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Taylor Instrument Companies, Rochester, New York. 1910-1930 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Linde Air Products Co., New York. 1919-1921 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Arthur L. Day, Corning Glass Works. May, 1920-August, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Bario Metal Corp., New York. 1920-1921 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Special Chemicals Co., Highland Park, Illinois. 1920-1921 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Standard Scientific Co., New York. 1920-1921 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: A. F. Wells Co., San Francisco. 1920-1925 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Leeds & Northrup Co., Philadelphia. 1920-1921, 1930, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Chicago Apparatus Co., Chicago. 1925-1927 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Keuffel & Esser Co., Hoboken, New Jersey. 1927-1936 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Ohio Chemical & manufacturing Co., Cleveland. 1931-1932 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Scott Paper Co., Chester, Pennsylvania. 1921-1936 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding equipment. 1906-1937 (Box 23, Folder 1-6)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding office supplies. 1910-1935 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence regarding slides and photographic materials. 1912-1936 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence regarding a motorcycle. 1911 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding automobiles. 1910-1934 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Lord Motor Car Co., Los Angeles. 1909-1914 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding automobiles licenses and insurance. 1915-1929 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Requests, 1910-1937
    - Requests for plants. 1910-1937 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Requests for seeds. 1910-1937 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Requests for plant identification. 1921-1935 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Requests for advice on plant selection. 1920-1934 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Requests for information regarding the Desert Laboratory. 1913-1937 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Requests for information regarding cactus. 1913-1937 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Requests for information regarding desert flora. 1913-1937 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Requests for information regarding the yucca fiber industry. 1914-1937 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Requests for information regarding plants in general. 1913-1937 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Requests for information regarding trees. 1914-1937 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Requests for information regarding sap flow in trees. 1921-1929 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Requests for information regarding artificial cell. 1922-1928 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Requests for information regarding equipment. 1920-1937 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Requests for information regarding climatic conditions. 1922-1937 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Requests for information regarding health problems. 1921-1934 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Requests for information regarding E. L. Larkin and Cell Life. 1922 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Requests for information regarding various people. 1916-1932 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Requests for information regarding the Salton Sea. 1920-1927 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Requests for information regarding solar radiation. 1920-1936 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Requests for miscellaneous information. 1913-1936 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Requests for advice and opinions regarding projects, publications, theories, study, etc. 1913-1937 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Requests for travel advice. 1919-1937 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence with Comte de Nouy, November 1926 and Nicholas Roosevelt, February 1930.
    - Requests for photographs, films, slides, etc. 1910-1937 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Requests for personal recommendations, references, and endorsements. 1920-1932 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Requests for information and recommendations concerning various publications. 1914-1937 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous requests. 1921-1934 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Requests for jobs. 1913-1937 (Box 25, Folder 7-9)
      Includes a job request from Donald Culross Peattie, March 6, 1925.
    - Requests for letters for introduction and recommendations. 1912-1936 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Desert Laboratory requests to fill positions. 1928-1931 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence Regarding Publications, Books, etc., 1907-1938
    - Correspondence: Requests for various and miscellaneous Carnegie Publications. 1913-1937 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Acknowledgments for Carnegie Publications. 1920-1931 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Publications requested by the Desert Laboratory. 1913-1937 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Publications (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Book orders. 1909-1938 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Stechert, G. E. 1907-1937 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Subscriptions. 1909-1935 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Book-binding. 1920-1938 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: John Crerar Library, Chicago. 1920-1937 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding books, publications, etc. 1910-1937 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: The Plant World. 1923-1937 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Series V: D. T. MacDougal Personal Papers, 1908-1935
  - Biographical Information for publications. 1923-1929 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: Family. 1920-1924 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: Stearns, Harold (family). 1920-1922 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: Austin, Mary. 1920-1924 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: Dutton, Louisa B., Carmel Library. 1920-1926 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: Fenner, Dr. H. W. 1916-1925 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: Heard, Dwight B. 1925-1929 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: Hoffmann, Bernhard. 1920-1923 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: Taylor, Henry O. 1921-1930 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: Livingston, Grace. June, 1920-November 1920 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Gulick, Sidney L. 1920-1921 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Flanders, Grace & Paul. 1921-1923 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Lowell, Amy. December 21, 1922-December 23, 1922 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Bechdolt, F. R. 1922-1928 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Martin, Anne. 1923-1924 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: James, D. L. 1925-1930 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Hunter, Mrs. Robert. October 1926-November 1926 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Kahofer, Jules. 1926-1929 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Vail, Anna Murray. 1925-1927 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Abbott, Lawrence F. February 1928-July 1928 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: DePauw University. 1920-1927 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: Art and pageants. 1920-1928 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Includes correspondence relating to the Arizona Pageantry Association, 1927-1928, with a letter from James McClintock.
  - Personal Correspondence: Books and subscriptions. 1920-1924 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: Miscellaneous. 1908-1959 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Property: Carmel, California. 1920-1925 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Property: Tucson, Arizona. 1920-1933 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Contributions. 1921-1930 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Includes correspondence regarding a 1923 Tokyo earthquake and the Arizona Hut, Inc.
  - Personal Correspondence: Articles in The Garden Magazine. 1921-1927 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: Alexander, Jerome regarding MacDougal's contribution to a book on colloid chemistry. 1920-1928 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: Ingalls, Albert G., Associate Editor of Scientific American regarding articles. 1925-1931 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: Various publications by MacDougal including requests for copies and reprints. 1913-1935 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Requests for MacDougal to write articles. 1915-1928 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Proposed publications. 1920-1929 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Includes correspondence with Frederick L. Allen of Harper & Brothers, 1924-1925, and John Farrar of George H. Doran Company, 1926-1929.
  - Memberships: American Philosophical Society. 1919-1930 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Includes correspondence regarding MacDougal's articles published in its Proceedings.
  - Memberships: California Academy of Sciences. 1916-1926 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Includes correspondence with Director, B. W. Evermann.
  - Memberships: Century Club, N. Y. 1920-1930 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Various memberships. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Memberships declined. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: Speeches. 1909-1931 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Speech: "Living Things and Physical Forces in Soils," New York Farmers. December 1924 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Includes correspondence with Secretary, Samuel Thorne.
- Series VI: Forrest Shreve Personal Papers, 1916-1937
  - Personal Correspondence: Various publications by Shreve including requests for copies and reprints. 1916-1937 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: The Cactus and Its Home. 1929-1937 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: Hannig, E. regarding Shreve's contributions to the publication Pflanzenareale. 1929-1930 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: "Rainfall, Runoff, and Soil Moisture Under Desert Conditions," Annals of The Association of American Geographers, v. 24. September 1934 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Shreve to write articles. 1930-1937 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Requests for Shreve to critique articles by others. 1930-1932 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: Proposed publications. 1929-1935 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Includes Shreve's "little handbook," The Desert, and a book to commemorate the Desert Laboratory's first 30 years.
  - Personal Correspondence: Speeches. 1931-1934 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: Family. 1928-1937 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: "The Education of Margaret," regarding his daughter's schooling, etc. 1928-1933 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Miscellaneous. 1928-1937 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Memberships. 1929-1936 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Property: Tucson and Carmel. 1928-1933 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Series VII: Desert Botanical Laboratory Plot Records, 1906-1985
  - Plot 4. February 16, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Plot 4. March 6, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Plot 4. January 30, 1978, February 15, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Plot 4. March 21, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Plot 7. February 21, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Plot 7. December 13, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Plot 7. March 31, 1978-April 4, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Plot 7. March 26, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Plot 9. February 21, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Plot 9. March 12, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Plot 9. January 5-7, 1978, January 25, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Plot 9. April 8, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Plot 10. February 21, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Plot 10. April 8, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Plot 10. April 7, 1968, April 10, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Plot 11. February 1906 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. April 1910 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. November 2, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. April 8, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. February 9, 1960, February 18, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. January 22, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. June 15-19, 1975, June 29, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. Spril 13-19, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 11. December 10-12, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Plot 12. February 24, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. February 27, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. April 1, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. March 1, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. January 31, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. June 1975 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. September 9-20, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. April 19, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. December 3, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 12. December 12-17, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Plot 14. February 26, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Plot 14. Aprill 2, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Plot 14. April 11-13, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Plot 14. April 11, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Plot 14. April 9, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Plot 15. May 1910 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. November 3, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. February 17, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. July 1936 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. November 1959 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. January 8, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. June 1975 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. April 21, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 15. December 18, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Plot 16. November 1, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. November 25, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. June 10, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. October 13-17, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. April 19, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. December 12, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. April 20, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 16. December 12, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Plot 17. April 2, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Plot 17. December 2, 1928 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Plot 17. February 24, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Plot 17. 1948 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Area B General: Legend, small sketches. 1928-1978 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Area B-1. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-1. March 16, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-1. 1948 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-1. March 26, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-1. January 12, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-1. February 15, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-1. June 1, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Area B-2. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-2. March 17, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-2. February 13, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-2. April 8, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-2. January 12, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-2. February 22, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-2. June 14, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Area B-3. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-3. March 16, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-3. 1948 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-3. April 22, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-3. January 12, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-3. February 22, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-3. June 14, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Area B-4. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-4. March 17, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-4. March 4, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-4. April 12, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-4. January 12, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-4. March 23, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-4. June 14, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Area B-5. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-5. March 4, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-5. February 14, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-5. April 25, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-5. January 15, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-5. March 28, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-5. June 15, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Area B-6. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-6. March 10, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-6. 1948 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-6. May 16, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-6. January 15, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-6. March 29, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-6. June 15, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Area B-7. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-7. March 4, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-7. 1948 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-7. April 27, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-7. January 15, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-7. March 28, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-7. June 14, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Area B-8. 1928 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Area B-8. March 10, 1936 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Area B-8. February 28, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Area B-8. June 3, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Area B-8. January 15, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Area B-8. March 29, 1978 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Area B-8. June 15, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 23)